'HARIKRISHNANS'
God bless you!
Have a nice vacation.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Should I write it as
Guptan or Guptadev?
I wouldn't mind
even if you write it as G.
I shall write it as Guptan.
Guptan, care of Mira, Hill Garden.
- Okay.
Thank you
for helping me check in here!
Please take him to the room.
I'm leaving.
When will I see you next?
I'll call you.
I'll visit you as well.
I'm really looking forward
to meeting that special person.
Did you travel
all by yourself, Ammalu?
Of course.
Brother will send me on a solo
world tour next year. - Oh, God!
Mr. Jose, this is Ammalu, the
one we told you about.
I see. They have told me
everything about you.
Though you're 11, you have the IQ
of a 20-year-old.
The topper of your class!
Exceptional in games
and sports as well!
One of the best
students of your school!
They told me
that you'd be here
for ten days to visit the place.
Roam around all you want.
But don't run into Gabriel.
Be careful!
He is a cannibal!
He is so strong that he could
take on ten men at once.
He is short-tempered.
He captures children, takes them
into the forest and eats them!
Please don't make a lot of noise.
He might climb
over the wall and come here.
Oh!
Aunt!
Uncle!
Mira is here!
What were you thinking, Mira?
Why did you travel almost
300 km all by yourself?
I'm not a kid anymore.
That's exactly my point.
You should be careful
now that you're an adult.
Wouldn't it hurt my pride
if you travel alone?
Why did you travel by bus, Mira?
Why didn't you give us a call?
Dad.. - Yes.
- Please explain it to mom.
Okay.
- There is nothing to explain.
Aunt, let me make it clear
that I don't approve of it.
Neither do I.
- What?
Hello. - How is it going?
Did you like the room?
Oh, it's you, Mira.
It's excellent.
When should we meet?
I'm good anytime.
Okay, I'll be there in the evening.
- Sure. - Bye.
"Oh, wind! Did you see those
ripe mangoes on those groves?"
"Could we swing on those lovely
vines? Does it have tender leaves?"
"Oh, dark cloud! You wear
bangles made of lightning."
"You swing on the rainbow.
Please come to me!"
"Come to me and let's fly
in the night sky"
"in search
of the lustrous moonlight."
"We've a beautiful
garden in the blue sky!"
"And we have a wonderful
home near a valley."
"A playhouse
that is filled with jubilation."
"Oh, dark cloud! You wear
bangles made of lightning."
"You swing on the rainbow.
Please come to me!"
"Come to me and let's fly
in the night sky"
"in search
of the lustrous moonlight."
"Once you've reached me, please
don't leave me anytime soon."
"Please don't vanish
far away. - Please don't."
"Please don't shed tears
when you feel resentment."
"Don't fade away without talking
to me. - Please don't disappear."
"You have the beautiful moonlight
for company. - The moonlight!"
"You have vivid dreams.
- Dreams!"
"And the melodious song
of the birds"
"echoes on those hills
adorned by sandalwood trees."
"On those hills adorned
by sandalwood trees."
Gabriel! - Oh, no! - Oh, my God!
- Run! - Ammalu, come on!
Okay.
Dress the wound and give her
an injection. - Yes, doctor.
Gabriel!
Escape!
- Run..
Come here.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Gabriel is not bad at all.
He is an innocent man.
He is deaf and dumb.
Mr. Jose, why do you spread
such rumours about Gabriel?
He is innocent.
But he can get scary at times.
Nonsense!
You know nothing at all.
What are you up to, Mira?
Kunjikuttan would not tell these
without a valid reason.
Whom do you meet at the hotel?
Hey, this is not America.
How can you roam around
with a man so freely?
I have tolerated enough.
Make it clear now!
Who is that fellow?
Why are you staring at me?
I am serious.
You can't do things as you wish!
Can I join you for a few days?
Of course.
Please come.
Hey!
Yes, I came on a bicycle.
If we call you
for a dinner party tonight
will you come?
Everyone wants to meet you.
Are you staying here alone?
Don't you have any relatives?
Who are they?
Where are they now?
Are they gone?
- Yes.
'If your daughter were alive,
she would have been my age.'
Hi. - I am Vishwambharan,
Mira's dad. - Oh.
I am Guptan.
Mira has told me everything.
She had a fight with her mom.
- She told me.
Your mom won't understand you
the way I do.
She is upset.
Come and pacify her.
I was about to come anyway.
- Then come along.
It was nice meeting you.
See you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Bye.
Please sit down.
"I have invited you to my house."
"What will you present me
in return, friend?"
"I will serve you food with love."
"Do relish it without hesitating,
friend!"
"I have hot rice for you.
- I have hot rice for you.."
"I have tasty gravy for you.
- I have tasty gravy for you.."
"You can enjoy the scenery here.."
"The lovely and beautiful scenery."
"Oh, dark cloud! You wear
bangles made of lightning."
"You swing on the rainbow.
Please come to me!"
"Come to me and let's fly
in the night sky"
"in search
of the lustrous moonlight."
That dumb Gabriel killed him
with a pickaxe.
'Dumb man arrested for murder
in Poonoor.'
No. Gabriel is not the killer.
It was not Gabriel!
'Smoking is injurious to health.'
Look, according to the post-mortem
report, the murder
happened between 10 p.m.
and 10.30 p.m. yesterday.
But Gabriel was with us
until midnight.
Then how is it possible?
We had invited Gabriel.
He had his dinner with us.
- Come here, dear.
Don't tell this to anyone.
- But..
Just forget about all this.
Okay?
But I am telling the truth.
Otherwise, you can ask them.
Dear, have you heard
of Mr. Vishwambharan?
He is the one who decides
everything here.
Going against him is just
inviting trouble.
Then we won't be there
to help you out.
No need.
I don't need anyone.
I will handle this myself.
I can also approach
Harikrishnan Associates.
Hey, don't push.
- Just move.
He is there.
- Come on!
Don't push.
Just let me through. - Hey!
Hey! - Sir..
Sir, what happened to the appeal
in the Kozhikode case?
Move..
I want to say something.
Sir, what is the status of the
Karunagappally case?
What are you saying?
Move aside!
I am a relative
of the judicial magistrate.
What happened to my case? - I'll
tell the magistrate to hang you.
Haven't I told you
to come to the office for queries?
Leave me!
Are the Harikrishnans inside?
Yes. They have arrived.
They are discussing a case.
Any woman would be scared
if her husband
comes home at night stealthily
like a thief.
When the wife started screaming
when he snatched her jewellery
the husband killed her ruthlessly.
Any wife will be afraid
when her husband
finds her lover hiding in her room.
Amidst the fight between the men
the wife was thrashed
and killed by mistake
while trying to help her lover.
She would have been killed
by her own lover!
Since there is not even a doubt
about the existence of such a lover
this argument can never be given
consideration.
Yes. But they can try all
possible ways.
But will this work out here,
Krishnan? - No way, Hari.
Then you can come down.
The only defence that the defendant
can bring out in this case
is to create an imaginary
lover. But it won't last.
So, Harikrishnan Associates can
take up this case.
Do not miss any of his points.
Let Simon take up this case.
- Okay.
The rascal who killed his wife
for gold
should get the maximum punishment.
- Yes, sir.
Take it as a challenge.
- Where is Mr. Sundaran?
I am here!
I am here itself..
Where were you until now?
I've been here a while.
But those idiots stopped me
at the entrance itself.
I didn't want to create a scene,
so.. - Enough.
We are leaving.
- You can come later. - Okay.
Who was the prosecutor?
- Mr. Hari.
Mr. Krishnan was defending.
Have you made a note of all
the points? - Yes.
Ammalu is calling from Poonoor!
Ammalu is calling!
- Sir..
Sir, what about my case?
- Move..
Hari here, Ammalu.
- Krishnan here. - What is it?
What? You want us to come there?
- Why, dear?
What is the matter?
Hey, we are busy here.
Is it important?
Okay, then. We are there.
Harikrishnan Associates
is an all India network
consisting of around 300 advocates.
Usually, they let their juniors
handle most of the cases.
But we don't have to get worried
if they are taking up
this case in person.
They will submit a bail petition
question the kids
who are the witnesses
and will then get bail.
Which means.. Harikrishnans have
taken up this case.
So we don't have to worry
about it anymore.
What the hell are you saying?
We have to confront Harikrishnans!
How can we take that lightly?
You see, Mr. Kunjikuttan.
Aren't they here to prove
that Gabriel is innocent?
And not to bring the actual
culprit before the law.
They would leave once
they have done their job.
Will they? Are you sure?
- They will leave.
However, if you learn that
they backed out of a case
that would mean that the game
has changed. You must be careful.
It means that they would leave
only once it is proven.
In the sense,
they would leave only
by ensuring that the culprit
is punished by the law.
In order to do so, they
have their own detective agency.
Yes.
Your Honour, I am Harikrishnan
from Harikrishnan Associates.
We appear for the accused.
Your Honour, I am also Harikrishnan
from Harikrishnan Associates.
I know.
Harikrishnans.
Yes. He is Harikrishnan,
and I am Harikrishnan.
I call him Hari,
and he calls me Krishnan.
And together we are Harikrishnan
of Harikrishnan Associates.
Okay. Proceed.
What is your name?
- Nisha.
Okay.
Do you know that man?
No.
Didn't all of you
throw him a party?
No.
Didn't he buy you
chocolates that day? - No.
Who gave you instructions
for these responses? Mom or dad?
Dad and mom.
You may leave.
Your Honour.
Gabriel and the kids were at a
party during the time of murder.
However, none of the kids' parents
are letting them speak the truth.
It is evident that someone
is behind this.
Hence, by taking Nisha's statements
into account as evidence, I request
the court to grant Gabriel
bail until further progress.
That is all, your Honour.
Yes.
Your Honour.
I would like to question
someone before the court
before granting
the accused with bail.
Who is that?
- Ammalu.
How long has it been since
you have arrived at Poonoor?
One week.
- Okay.
How are you related
to the Harikrishnans?
Hari is my brother.
They say that despite her age, she
has the maturity of a 21-year-old.
Who has said so?
My class teacher, principal
and many more. - Okay.
How much were you graded
in the subject English?
100 percent.
- Very good.
In that case,
I have a doubt.
Will you clarify it for me?
- Yes.
What is the difference
between love and like?
I love my brother.
- Okay.
And I like ice cream.
Do you love him or like him?
I love him.
What kind of love?
Love.
That's all.
Did you go over to Gabriel's place?
Yes.
Did you enter his room?
- Yes.
Were there anybody
else at his place? - No.
Did he leave the door open
or lock it from inside?
He locked it from inside.
Did Gabriel touch you?
Yes.
- Where did he touch you?
He first touched my cheek..
- And?
What did he do to you?
Did he take you in his arms?
Did he hug you?
Come on, tell me!
He hugged me.
- Okay.
If an 11-year-old has the
maturity of a 21-year-old
it is certain that she would
have the feelings of a 21-year-old.
I state before the court
that there exists an illicit
relationship between Gabriel
and the child that doesn't
comply with society's notions.
Also, I state that
the brilliant mind
such as Ammalu is
Harikrishnan's solution
to bail their client.
She is a liar
before the law.
Your Honour, if we bail
an accused for the sake
of a child, that will only..
Let me go..
- Please don't.
It is unfair that he doesn't
let a lawyer plead his case.
Get lost. Take him.
- Get here! - Take him!
Get off me. - Let him go.
- No!
No, Hari. Let's go.
Let's leave, Krishna.
Take him.
Please drop the case.
Let us leave.
Take him.
- Keep walking.
Let us leave.
Let us go.
Your Honour.
We are backing out of this case.
They backed out?
What does that mean?
Lawyer!
Am I going to be screwed?
If the Harikrishnans have backed
out from a case
it doesn't comply only one,
but has many meanings to it.
The first being that they have
set for something even bigger.
Can you look at my
face while you speak?
And the second being that they are
going to open an office for it.
And the third being that they
won't rest until this case is over.
Which means..
- Which means I am screwed.
...that is the fourth meaning.
- What?
Why didn't you want us to
proceed with the case, Ammalu?
The case is only beginning,
isn't it?
Just consider that Ammalu
helped us find
and bring a dangerous man
before the law,
who was in hiding all the while.
We would leave only once
the case is settled.
Really?
- Yes.
"Oh, beautiful moon.
A thousand.."
A thousand eyes gaze at you."
"Oh, the treasure of heaven!
Come to the sky."
"We'll steal that melodious song"
"of the cuckoo's lips for you."
"We'll let you witness the shining
light of a thousand lamps."
"The dark clouds
will adorn your soft cheeks."
"Oh, beautiful moon.
A thousand eyes gaze at you."
"Oh, the treasure of heaven!
Come to the sky."
"We'll steal that melodious song"
"of the cuckoo's lips for you."
"We'll let you witness the shining
light of a thousand lamps."
"The dark clouds
will adorn your soft cheeks."
"Even though you are silent now,
we know you love to converse."
"It is so pleasing
to listen to your beautiful voice."
"Oh, dragonfly! Your lips"
"have the fragrance
of a beautiful flower."
"Oh, glowworm. You have
the whole night for yourself"
"and the dazzling
moonlight for company."
"Oh, beautiful moon.
A thousand eyes gaze at you."
"Oh, the treasure of heaven!
Come to the sky."
"The mischievous kitten
and its playmates"
"winked at you as they wanted
to make friends with you."
"The crow sang a song,
and it wants to whisper"
"something in your ears
about your marriage."
"No, you shouldn't
go anywhere."
"This beautiful child is ours."
"Oh, beautiful moon.
A thousand eyes gaze at you."
"Oh, the treasure of heaven!
Come to the sky."
"We'll steal that melodious song"
"of the cuckoo's lips for you."
"We'll let you witness the shining
light of a thousand lamps."
"The dark clouds
will adorn your soft cheeks."
"Better than the
entire world"
"is our India."
"Better than the
entire world.."
"We are its nightingales"
"and it is our garden abode."
The precision of the murders
committed by Vishwambharan.
He has been involved in 12 murders
in the past 24 years.
All 12 of them have been
done with such perfection.
Each one of them has
an Hitchcockian style.
Hitchcock?
I didn't sign?
What do you mean by
Hitchcockian style?
It means that the culprit
could be found right away.
Just like he showed Gabriel
to us as the culprit.
So the story goes like this.
Vishwambharan's daughter Mira
comes here, accompanied
by her lover Guptan.
The two lovers roam
around the village.
Vishwambharan was not at all
interested in this relationship.
He tried opposing it many times
but wasn't successful.
Mira had even slept
with Guptan at a hotel room.
Is it?
When did that happen?
On the night of November 26.
Mr. Vishwambharan, who
couldn't take this anymore
decided to kill Guptan
and put the blame on the deaf-mute.
So, Vishwambharan is not
destroying any of the evidence.
Instead, he is intentionally
giving us all the evidence.
Still, against whom should
we use that pickaxe
which was used as an
important evidence
in trying to prove that
Gabriel was the culprit?
We should place that pickaxe
on Vishwambharan's hands.
It would perfectly
match his hands.
Was there any need to come here
and open an office
for such a silly case?
This case is really a simple
and straightforward one.
Somebody tries to kill
Guptan in his hotel room
by injecting a
poisonous substance
which even our lab
couldn't identify until now.
Then throws him down
from the third floor
and finally stabs him using
a pickaxe. It's as simple as that.
It becomes even simpler when we've
a post-mortem report that couldn't
specify if the death happened
because of the poison
or being stabbed or by falling
from the third floor.
Also, we have
a useless investigation report.
It's as simple as that.
What do you have to say about Mira?
Her character is a bit confusing.
She strongly testified
against Gabriel at the court
even after knowing that
her dad was behind this.
Vishwambharan might
have threatened her.
Shouldn't we meet her, Hari?
- Yes.
She refuses to meet us whenever
we ask for an appointment.
Doesn't she visit
anyone or anywhere?
There is a place she visits
every evening.
A British library.
So, we are meeting
her today. Aren't we?
Hari, we are being followed
by that car for a long time.
Give them room.
Let them go ahead.
They are not passing us.
Somebody isn't happy
with us meeting her.
They would've decided to leave
us as we are two simple lawyers.
Mira.
- Mira.
Good morning, Mira.
- Good morning.
We are..
- Harikrishnans.
So you know us.
But you might be confused about
who is Hari and who
is Krishnan among us.
So don't get confused. I'm Hari.
I'm Krishnan.
So let's come to the
matter, shall we? - Yes.
Come on.
We are aware that this
is a moment of grief for you.
Unfortunately, we are also involved
in the same case which
saddens you. - Yes.
To make matters worse,
we are appearing
as the defence lawyers
in the court. - Exactly.
To start with,
we first met that deaf-mute
whom your dad blames
for the murder. - Yes.
We asked him everything.
He is innocent.
Even you are aware of it.
Not just you, even your dad
and everyone else is aware of it.
Then for whom is he getting
tortured like this?
You should give us an answer.
I want to ask you
the same thing.
For whom did he take
the blame upon himself?
Who forced him to do all this?
I want to know it, too.
You might think that my
dad is behind all this.
I would've believed you if you had
told me about it a long time back.
I grew up, seeing my dad
do all kinds of illegal things.
It made me question
everything in life.
For the past seven-eight years
I'm sure that my dad
hasn't done anything wrong.
It was I who influenced
the public prosecutor.
So, even after knowing
that he is innocent
for whom did you insult that
poor little girl in the court..
And tried to reject the bail
of a deaf..
- And dumb person?
For what reason?
I-I didn't think that the public
prosecutor would do all this.
I'm sorry for that.
Gabriel should be in jail
until we catch the real culprit.
It is necessary for me.
So you know who
is behind the murder.
We don't understand why
you are trying to hide
the guy who is behind
the murder of your lover.
There are many things
that you wouldn't understand.
Why should I tell you,
the defence lawyers?
We are on opposite
sides in this case.
Don't forget that
while asking your questions.
Krishnan. - Yes?
- It's very confusing.
One thing is for sure.
- What?
We can remove Vishwambharan
from the list. - For sure.
He is not involved in this case.
But this Mira..
She is mysterious.
- Yes.
Ammalu has entrusted us
with a very tricky case.
Together, we will walk upon
the path filled with mysteries.
Hari.
- Krishnan.
Yes, we got it.
We found two old cases in which
Vishwambharan was involved.
To hell with it.
Throw it away.
We don't require it anymore.
He is now transforming
himself into a Gandhian.
Discard this file
and start a new one.
Whose?
- Guptan's.
Guptan, the one who is dead?
We are not able to find the details
of the living,
let alone this dead guy.
We have to find it immediately.
Harikrishnans Associates!
Networks all over India!
And yet, nobody could find
any details about Guptan.
There is absolutely no information!
Nonsense!
Did he fall from the sky?
We received the specimen
re-examination report from Delhi.
They couldn't identify the
details about the poison yet.
Not yet?
- No.
Where is this case heading to?
Did you tell Hari?
- Yes.
It seems that Guptan doesn't
belong to this planet.
It seems that he came
from some other planet.
Did you inquire about Mira's
cousin, Mr. Kunjikuttan?
He is good for nothing.
Should we inquire about him?
No, leave him alone for now.
He might send for us.
But Guptan.. - We cannot even
find his address.
It's Guptan, care of Mira
at the police station.
at the hotel.
It's Guptan, care of Mira
even in the post-mortem report.
Only while receiving his body,
it's written as Mira.
What could be a solution for this?
How many ambulances would
be there in Poonoor?
I didn't think in that way.
Now you have to start
thinking in that way.
Who are you?
- Are you an ambulance driver?
Antony, right?
- Yes.
Guptan's body was
taken in your ambulance
after the post-mortem
on the 27th of last month.
I don't know anyone called Guptan.
We have lots of work
to do after this.
Try to remember.
I deal with dead bodies every day.
I never remember these things.
Now, just try to remember it.
Yes, try to remember.
Just think about it.
Come on, Antony.
Tell us.
- Yes, I will.
Mira had told me to keep it
as a secret. - That's okay.
I took it to a place
200 km away from here.
Where?
To the Killikal palace.
Killikal palace.
"Magical palace."
Oh, God!
Who are you?
- We are Guptan's..
Why are you
trying to scare us?
I was scared.
We are advocates
enquiring about Guptan.
Who lives here?
Myself, my Lord and a servant.
That's all.
So are you the youngest of the lot?
In a way. - So are you
not directly related? - No.
So let the Lord know that two
advocates are here to meet him.
'This magnificent evening.'
Hari.
- Yes?
'This magnificent evening.'
Keep it..
What is it now?
Who are you?
Why do you want to meet me?
They want to ask the same
questions and hurt me. That's all.
What's the use in talking now?
Can you give my Guptan back to me?
Can you?
The ones who murdered
my innocent son
are freely walking the streets.
Can you get them to me alive?
You may talk to me after that.
Can you?
We will present
whoever is responsible
for your son's death
at your feet
within ten days.
What is it, Hari?
Why are you giving him hope?
Fine..
Forgive me if I was rude.
You did not mention your names.
My name is Harikrishnan.
- Okay.
I am also Harikrishnan.
What is this?
This is nice.
You are both renowned advocates.
Is it the two of you?
- Yes..
Why didn't you mention that?
This is Ramappan.
He is a distant relative
from my mother's side.
He has two children in Chennai.
One among them is a doctor.
They are here on learning
of Guptan's demise.
All of them grew up together.
As Guptan was crazy
about travelling
Ramappan and his kids
gave me company.
What do you want to know?
Ask me.
We wanted to be familiar
with Guptan's life.
We also wanted to know what
you had to say about him.
We got a few hints on our way here.
We came to know that
he was an introvert
and a very talented person.
We came to know that he sang well.
What are you saying?
He just had to touch the Veena.
He would create divine music.
He was a poet, a singer
a scholar and much more.
Didn't you notice
the decorations outside?
Today is the festival of lights.
The festival at the temple
also starts today.
This will be a festival
without my son for the first time.
After the lamps are lit,
and the festival is started
venerations for the Goddess
will be performed for nine days.
The Goddess will be pleased by
singing songs on the tenth day
and will be welcomed to our
home from the temple.
My Guptan did that.
My son would stand in front
of the Goddess.
I would bathe
and bless him wholeheartedly.
As the rightful heir of the house
he will let go of everything
including wealth
and power and become pure.
He will become a nomad.
The Goddess, pleased
by music and lights
would permit us
to live for a year
and return after
giving back the wealth.
That is the custom here.
Guptan had accepted the wealth
and sang songs for the Goddess
for the past 20 years.
On the night of the tenth day
this year
who is there to please
the Goddess with music?
Whom shall I bless
as per tradition?
Who will accept the wealth
from the Goddess?
Please don't worry, your Majesty.
Guptan will come back.
What are you saying?
He said that he would bring
the one who murdered Guptan.
Now you say that Guptan
will come back.
Let him come.
Even I want the same
in my heart.
I can't accept the fact
that he won't return.
He will come, sir.
He will come.
Hari wants to ask you
some questions.
Yes. What do you
want to know? Ask me.
Did Guptan have any close friends?
He was a loner.
He came with a few
college students recently
and stayed for two days.
The house was filled with music
and poetry. They had a good time.
That's when I came to know
that Guptan was a visiting
professor in some college.
Which was the college?
He mentioned some name.
I forgot it.
Can you try to remember it?
No. I did not take it seriously.
Was anyone else close to Guptan?
Yes.
If Guptan was alive
he would have been
married by this time.
He never wanted to get married
but he told me recently
that a girl, who I might like
would be with him
to celebrate this festival.
What did he say
about that girl?
He just mentioned the name Mohini.
Was it Mohini or Mira?
No. It was Mohini.
Mohini Varma.
What is it?
Why are you shocked? - No.
It's nothing, sir.
- Okay.
We want to visit
Guptan's bedroom and study room.
Of course. The room is upstairs
on the east facing end.
Nothing has been changed.
Everything is intact.
Please proceed.
- Okay. - Yes.
His dad did not make a mistake.
It was not Mira either.
We were the ones who
made a mistake.
Mohini Varma is not fictitious.
I have found the letters
she wrote to Guptan.
So have I.
Mohini Varma is
part of a riddle.
She truly loved and admired Guptan.
She is either equally talented
or may be better than Guptan.
You may take these
and keep it there.
Move it.
What?
Did you see everything?
Yes. We are leaving, sir.
What is this?
You came to my house
and are leaving
without staying or having a meal..
- We have lots of work, sir.
We are taking the letters and
poems written by Mohini to Guptan.
We will return it.
Do you mind? - No problem.
But when you leave so soon..
- We will be back soon.
Didn't I tell you?
This is Ramappan's son.
Dr. Jaikumar.
I am Hari.
I am Krishnan.
This is my brother, Premkumar.
Hello.
- I'm Hari.
I'm Krishnan.
We shall leave.
What is it?
Are you here to question me?
No. But we have to.
Nice. This is the apt place
to dispel guilt.
I'm asking you something
out of the blue.
Did Guptan have another lover?
Not another lover.
He had only one lover.
Mohini Varma.
So you knew about Guptan
and Mohini Varma
but you hid it.
Why?
What is this, Hari?
Mira will have her own reasons.
Mira loved Guptan.
But Guptan loved Mohini.
Any woman would lose her mind
when she knows that the guy
she loves is in love
with another woman.
Yes.
- If you can't convince your lover
you may even harm him.
If you have a wealthy dad
you may blame someone and escape.
You may build and live in a
pretty cabin to dispel your guilt.
When smart advocates
argue using these points
you will be trapped.
How were you related to Guptan
who came to Poonoor after
accepting Mohini's invitation?
I was only a friend
who helped Guptan
in finding Mohini,
whom he never met.
Do you hear her, Hari?
Mira and Guptan were just friends.
Do you get it?
Why did you spend a night
with him in a hotel?
Shame on you!
Two advocates who are
famous all over the nation.
Now I know how narrow
your minds are.
If Hari and Krishnan
share the same room
is there anything immoral in it?
You cannot believe
that a guy and a girl
can spend time together morally.
It's because you cannot
be like that.
But Guptan could do that.
So could I.
We discussed
Mohini's letters and poems.
We spent a whole night
in the hotel room.
It's true.
But we shared his dreams
about Mohini.
Not the bed.
I've known Guptan
for just a few days.
We became close
on our first meeting itself.
The books we read were similar.
We had like thoughts.
Even the topics for our research
were the same.
I wanted him to be my mentor.
But he wanted us to be friends.
You guys don't know
who and what he was.
We know some of it.
Guptan was an eccentric who knew
the highs and lows of life.
At the same time,
a great dreamer.
While he was studying
for his MA in Indore
Mohini was doing
her first year of her BA.
She wrote many letters to Guptan
from Delhi.
A poor girl who was trapped
by some people.
It might be her husband
or some gangsters.
Anyway, she was held
in a gilded cage.
She wrote many poems to escape
from the pain.
She wanted a life with him.
Guptan loved her poems.
He loved her through them.
He went to Poonoor
when she asked him to come.
This is what we know.
You know the rest.
Even I know only this much.
We went searching for her
in Poonoor.
But we couldn't find her.
She is hiding somewhere.
I want to find her.
I want to know why she invited him
and made him fall in love.
We should save her
if she is innocent.
We should punish her
if she is found guilty.
I am clear about one thing.
If everyone comes to know that
the investigation is against her..
She or the ones who are hiding
her might escape from here. - Yes.
That is the reason
why you portrayed Gabriel
as the culprit and hid everything,
isn't it? - Yes.
You wish to keep her name
out of this case.
Yes.
- Okay.
As we have started to understand
each other
we would never stand against
your wishes.
Apart from that
we will find Mohini Varma for you
in nine days.
Okay?
- Yes.
But a lot of her letters
are missing.
No. I have them.
Can we see them?
It's at home.
Okay, then we will come
in the morning..
Yes.. at 10 in the morning.
Can we leave now?
We know that some of our questions
may have bothered you.
Which one?
The one about the bed?
Well.. - Please forgive us, it's
the trait of being advocates.
No hard feelings.
- Hey, never mind.
So can we leave? - Okay, bye..
- See you.
Why trouble that poor Gabriel..
Can't you release him today itself?
- Sure..
Why did you stop the car?
You asked me to stop.
- Did I?
You did, didn't you?
Why?
I wanted to take a leak.
Make it fast.
- Sure.
Finally, I found out
that it was worth the long wait.
Mira was born for me.
I have to thank Ammalu
for everything.
Her face..
I felt that pinch of love
at the very first sight.
That closeness..
Ammalu, thank you so much
for bringing Mira into my life.
The tree which is shy to blossom.
The day that forgot to end.
It's like a new feeling found me.
What's going on?
Are you flooding the place?
It's been a while.
Aren't you done yet?
I'm done..
I'm coming.
I was thinking of getting
Gabriel out.
Me too.
Come..
- Come.
A random college.
A visiting professor
had taught there.
He was a poet, vocalist,
philosopher and a gentleman.
He was close with a six-member
gang of students.
Which college was it?
Who was the professor?
Who were the students?
Find these out and report it
to Sundaran.
All information from Chennai Agency
will be strictly confidential.
It should only be handled by Hari,
Sundaran and me.
Okay?
- Okay.
Read this.
Who monitors the data
from Chennai? - Stephen does.
Should we ask anything of Mira?
I think we don't have to.
Yes. Her thoughts and decisions
are strange.
Then again, it has helped us
to a certain extent.
How? - Isn't it because of her
suing Gabriel
that Ammalu summoned us?
Didn't it pan out well?
Yes.. I've promised
to meet with her tomorrow.
Yes. We will meet her
tomorrow at 10 a.m.
Yes. Maybe around 10:30 a.m.
Drat!
Krishnan!
- Yes?
Mira is mine!
- Mira is mine!
Fantastic! Great!
Great, indeed!
- Isn't it?
So Mira is mine!
- No. Mira is mine alone.
Stop kidding.
I decided
when I saw her up close.
I made the decision when I
saw her from a distance.
Stop joking, Krishnan.
I'm serious.
- I'm even more serious.
Quit it, will you?
I know that you
are pulling my strings. - No.
I'm saying this from
the bottom of my heart.
Mira is mine!
No! She is mine!
Am I not older by a year or so?
That is based on the records.
You are much older.. - Leave it..
It has already been decided.
- Yes.
It is!
If Kallookkaran Vishwambharan
has a daughter named Mira
she is mine! She's for advocate
Harikrishnan alias Krishnan!
You can kiss your dreams goodbye.
Krishnan, if I am Hari
of Harikrishnans Associates
I won't kiss anything goodbye
and no guy named Krishnan
is going to get
Vishwambharan's daughter Mira.
Key..
- Thank you..
Okay.
So you love Mira.
Yes.
- How much?
A lot.
- Is it as vast as the sky?
Yes. - So your love for her
is as vast as the sky.
Now ask me how much I love her.
Ask me.
- I'm not going to.
Why?
- I prefer not to. - Hey!
Why are you being a baby about it?
Mira is the only girl
for me in this lifetime.
Mine too.
- Okay.
Krishnan, this is meant to be.
Or else why didn't I even think
of even getting married?
That's because you couldn't
find a girl!
Me? Really?
Who do you think you are?
Prince Charming?
What girl in her right mind
will be attracted
by your crooked teeth,
gummy smile
those giant nasal openings
and your horsey gait?
What?
- Girls will fly down from Egypt
and line up for you on seeing
your pumpkin-like cheeks,
squishy nose
and your lopsided gait.
Cover that nose, Krishnan.
Let some girls look at your face.
Enough..
Don't overdo it..
Oh, sorry.
What is this special ritual?
This was taught to me
by my grandmother.
To find answers to
unanswerable questions.
How do you do it?
If the leaf falls on 'Yes',
I'll meet Mohini Varma.
But the leaf fell on 'No'.
It means I am not going
to meet Mohini.
It has never gone wrong.
Harikrishnans cannot bring
Mohini Varma in front of me.
Let's see.
You can try.
But it is not going to happen.
Let me clean it.
Nobody is supposed to see this.
Take your seat.
Let's have a cup of tea.
You are well prepared, Mira.
We are friends now.
We are more than friends.
- Yes, even more than that.
Can we see the letters and poems
written by Mohini?
I will give it to you.
Please sit down.
People need to have good taste
in literature to enjoy poetry.
Yes.. I have good knowledge
of literature since childhood.
I am sorry.
No. I will clean it.
Oh, no.
I am sorry.
You have spilt it, too.
You are similar to each other.
Have your tea.
It's really hot.
Let it cool down.
I started to boil tea like this
after I met Guptan.
He used to love having tea
when it was served hot.
These are the letters and poems
written by Mohini.
Have your tea.
Guptan had set aside the most
beautiful 20 poems from Mohini.
He wanted to publish them with her
permission after meeting her.
We can't publish these poems
without her permission.
It would be a great loss
to Malayalam literature
if they don't get published.
Your wish to adorn Malayalam
literature with these poems
will be fulfilled at any cost.
I will be the one to do..
- We will do it for you.
I hope you can accomplish this
as soon as possible.
We badly want to accomplish
that.
Yes, we will do it.
Mira, we are taking these poems
with us.
Don't lose it somewhere.
- I won't.
Mira.
- Yes.
Which wood did you use
to make that bridge?
Which bridge?
That one.
Please come here.
Mira, one minute.
Did you make these house
based on ancient architecture
or according to the techniques
used by the Japanese?
It's an ordinary..
- Mira.
Where did you get that
Mexican snow flower? Please come.
Krishnan. We need to go.
We have work to do. Come on.
Okay, bye.
Even though we met
during a legal battle
but we have a relationship..
- Hari, we should go.
We have work to do.
- Yes. We need to go.
You can expect any kind of help
from me.
It can be anything.
- As a friend, he will help you.
Yes. As a friend, I will help you.
- Yes, as a friend.
As a friend.
When I offered to help Mira
whenever she needs me
why was it necessary to bring
friendship in between that?
Yes, it is necessary.
It is not right to talk to a girl
like that.
What is wrong?
- It is wrong.
It is a vulgar statement.
- Let it be vulgar.
I was talking to Mira,
not to your wife.
What if I marry her in future?
She will get married.
But she will be my wife.
Don't talk nonsense.
- Who is talking nonsense now?
You are the one who claimed a girl
as his wife without her consent.
I said that. Don't talk to me
again, Krishnan.
You can leave, Krishnan. I will
take care of this case. - No.
You can leave. I will take care
of this alone.
This case is related to my sister.
I will take care of it.
I didn't transfer this case to you.
Harikrishnan Associates
are not related to this case.
It's true. Let's stop this company
forever from today.
We are departing forever.
Harikrishnan Associates is closed.
But I will take care of this case.
Let's see
who will plead this case.
Let's see.
Yes. Let's see.
Will you take photographs
of people travelling in cars?
I will.
Hari!
What is the matter?
Why do you take photographs
of people travelling in cars?
I didn't do it.
Krishnan!
Move!
I took the photographs.
- Nothing official about it.
Come here..
Let's have a duel.
We took your photographs
because you were following us.
Who sent you to follow us?
Tell me..
Tell us about it.
Tell us before we lose patience.
Else, we will go mad.
We are mad now.
Start the vehicle. - What?
- Start the vehicle!
Take us to Kunjikuttan.
We're taking a nap.
Don't wake us.
Where are the others?
Tell me what happened.
Did you mess them up?
Where did the lawyers
run off to?
I have brought them. - What?
- They are in the car.
What are they doing in the car?
My God. Sasi, what happened?
They are dead, Sasi.
Now I have murdered more people.
What do I do?
Sasi, they are dead.
We are not dead.
We were killed.
What?
- We are not dead. We were killed..
I didn't tell you to kill them.
What did you do?
- Kunjikuttan!
We should settle that murder case.
- I don't know anything.
Guptan's murder case.
Did you forget?
Don't forget that you're
talking to Harikrishnans.
You should forgive everything
and save me.
The two of you should settle
this case for me.
Sure. You might get 20 years
of rigorous imprisonment
and then the death penalty.
My God.
- We can fix all that.
Instead of the 20 years
of rigorous imprisonment
you will get the death penalty.
- That's enough. My God!
If you have the desire to live
we'll get rid of the
death penalty too.
But, you should tell us the truth
about what happened to Guptan.
I killed him.
- That's what we're talking about.
What did you say?
- I killed him.
Who did you kill?
- Guptan.
How?
- I kicked him hard.
Why? - I'll tell you the truth.
- Tell us.
I killed him so I can marry
my prospective bride. - Is that so?
He was trying to seduce her.
She lived with her in a hotel room.
He was talking to two people when
I went to visit him at the hotel.
I waited for an hour.
I went inside after they left.
What happened?
He was drunk and unconscious.
I kicked him hard.
I didn't think that the
kick would be fatal.
He died immediately
without even a struggle.
I don't know what I did.
I was out of control.
I dropped the body from the top
to make it look like a suicide.
I used Gabriel's axe on the body
to make it look like it was him.
I tried several things,
but nothing worked.
I did all this so I
can marry my Mira.
You can't marry her anyway.
- Why is that?
Tell him, Krishnan. I can't.
- I'll tell you.
Come with me.
Since you've told us so much
we should tell you the truth.
- Yes.
We are trying our best
to marry Mira.
What? - It's true.
You must be so happy.
If all three of us fight for Mira,
it won't be good.
If you back off this case,
we'll take care of the murder case.
I have already backed out.
- I need to ask you something.
Come
- I told you I'm done.
Come. We have to talk.
You told me that there were
two people with Guptan that day.
Could you recognise them again?
Yes. If I see them in person.
Kunjikuttan, we'll show them
or their photographs to you.
If you tell anyone that
we were looking for them
we'll make sure that
you get the death penalty.
Let's go and pee.
- I've already peed.
I need to pee.
- Go and take a piss, go. - Come.
Is Guptan handsome?
- He is very smart.
Is he as good as us?
- Not that much..
What does Guptan wear often?
When I saw him, a loose Kurta,
pants, glasses, and a shoulder bag.
Does he wear glasses?
- Yes.
You haven't peed yet.
Sometimes,
I pee in gaseous form.
Right now, I'm peeing in gaseous
form. That's why you can't see it.
Give us a lift in that
useless vehicle of yours.
Sure.
- Sasi!
Sasi!
Did you know?
- What?
Mira is going to get married.
It's not like I say every time.
I'll make sure it happens.
You've been saying this
for a long time.
This won't happen.
Get that in your head.
This will happen, Uncle.
I agree.
Everyone knows that.
But Mira won't agree.
Aunt, Mira will say yes.
She likes them.
Aren't you talking about yourself?
Not me. I backed out.
I'm talking about Harikrishnans.
Who are they?
- They like Mira very much.
This couldn't have been a reality
if I had married Mira.
Both of them take turns
to love her.
We can't give her to the both
of them. - We'll do a coin toss.
You were right.
Kunjikuttan didn't do anything.
He thinks that he
committed the murder.
Even if it is a murder or
suicide, this was a result
of the relationship
between Guptan and Mohini.
That is why we should find
the mystery behind Mohini Varma.
There is a Mohini
who fooled Lord Shiva.
One of Lord Vishnu's incarnations.
Maybe it is something like that.
Did you see?
- Yes.
Kunjikuttan recognised them.
But there is more.
This is the report from Chennai.
On the day Guptan was murdered
and the day before that
he was taking part in a meeting
where the Governor was the guest.
Yes. There is a copy of the minutes
of that meeting in this.
Mr. Sundaran.
Harikrishnans might
fail in this case.
No. That won't happen.
I'll look for loopholes.
Both of you need some rest.
Set aside the case for a while
and think about something else.
Look here.
"I'll give you"
"a lot of cases."
"Take rest,
happy Harikrishnans."
Go. Take rest.
I'm not going to take rest.
I'm going fishing..
And you? - I haven't decided,
but I'm going to the restroom now.
Where are you going?
You can't take rest. Sit down.
Hello.
- Yes, I'm Hari.
Which Hari?
I'm Hari from Harikrishnans.
- What is the matter?
I..
- What happened?
Nothing..
I need to see you.
We need to talk.
Where do you want to meet?
- Wherever.
Wherever you like..
Wherever you like.
- At what time?
At 5:00 p.m.
- Sure.
I'll meet you near Lake View.
- Okay.
I'll be waiting.
Was it them?
I told you.
That would also be them.
Hello.
- This is Krishnan.
What is the matter?
- I need to see you.
At what time? - We will..
- Is 5 p.m. okay?
Oh, yes..
We'll meet at 5 p.m.
Where do you want to meet?
Someplace you like.
Okay. Then we'll meet
at Lake View at 5 p.m.
Okay. Fine.
Hari has also told me
to meet me there.
Which Hari?
- Hari of Harikrishnans.
Hasn't he told you?
- Y-Yes.
H-He had told me..
Okay. We'll meet there.
Okay..
Okay.
I'm tired.
I'm tired of thinking
about this case all the time.
I need to get my mind relaxed.
I'm going to a movie.
- Which movie?
'Interesting Jack.'
Is it?
- Yes.
It's an awesome movie.
You must definitely see it.
Haven't you seen it yet?
- No, I'm going to see it today.
It will start in few minutes.
- Then go fast. - Yes.
Ammalu!
Hi, Krishnan.
Take this first.
I want your help.
Don't tell him that I told you.
You have to block Hari somehow
between 4:45 p.m.
and 5:45 p.m. today evening.
I..
- Don't ask me why..
We're doing this for a case..
Please.
Good evening, Hari.
I'm stuck with this crossword
for the last two days.
I want your help to complete this.
Crossword?
No way. I'm very busy today.
No, I won't let you leave.
Yuck! What kind of dress is this?
This is convenient for walking.
Didn't you tell me to visit you
after 5 p.m. if I needed help?
Yes, but we changed our
office time till 6 p.m.
I don't care. Come.
- Listen to me.
Come!
Hari hasn't come.
No, right?
Don't expect him to come now.
Hari does not have the habit
of keeping his word.
He keeps blabbering.
What can I do?
I can't complain
since he is my friend.
You said you had something
to say to me, right?
Yes. I'll tell you.
I was about to tell you.
The matter which I have to say is..
That is..
I asked you to meet me.
That is something
which anyone can ask you.
The main intention of what
I'm trying to say is..
I..
If I get something to drink
I would be happy to tell you.
Is this good enough for you?
Now you can tell me.
The thing which I
have to tell you is..
That is..
Our case..
Our investigation
to find the evidence..
And these pretty valleys
that provide the ambience
for our investigation.
The flock of sheep
which comes that way.
The river stream
that flows with poise.
The breeze that traverses
through the river.
The breeze flows..
Flows..
Krishnan, how was the movie?
Drop Ammalu back home.
Make it quick.
Why?
You should drop her
since this was your plan.
What are you talking about?
She's very tired
after having those chocolates.
What chocolate?
Who gave it to her?
We'll discuss it later.
Now go and drop her. - Why?
Just go!
I'll go. But why are
you talking nonsense?
What chocolates?
Come on, dear.
Mira, I'll come back now.
What was he saying?
No. Nothing.
He was describing the
beauty of nature.
During his college days
he has memorised many
dialogues about nature's beauty.
He keeps blabbering it.
I can't say anything
since he's my friend.
You said you had something
to say to me.
Yes.
I have something to say to you.
It is not something
very complicated.
But I have to tell you personally.
When I say this to you
you would understand why
I asked you to come here.
But before I tell you..
Do you need something to drink?
Yes. That would be great.
Now tell me.
Get down..
That is..
I discovered recently
that there is a budding
poet within me.
Guptan's poems are wonderful.
Here. You may not
have seen this one.
I memorised it.
I shall read it now.
See if you have heard this before.
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"
"Oh, eloquence!
You emerged within me"
"like a wave of beauty."
"My mind is a sanctuary
to many a nostalgic song."
"Your voice is a pleasant sound
that bloomed within me back then."
"Why are you not talking to me,
then?"
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"
"Oh, eloquence!
You emerged within me"
"like a wave of beauty."
"The full moon welcomes you."
"The nightly birds sing
along with your footsteps."
"My mind awaits your consent."
"I await your arrival."
"Won't you come,
beautiful eloquence?"
"I stay silent on a dark night
as the moonlight."
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"
"Oh, eloquence!
You emerged within me"
"like a wave of beauty."
"Why veil yourself,
my silent love?"
"Why shroud yourself
like a stranger?"
"You are what I sought
throughout this journey."
"You are the essence
of my favourite song."
"Won't you come,
playing your heavenly music?"
"The spring has come.
Do come, my dear."
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"
"Oh, eloquence!
You emerged within me"
"like a wave of beauty."
"My mind is a sanctuary
to many a nostalgic song."
"Your voice is a pleasant sound
that bloomed within me back then."
"Why are you not talking to me,
then?"
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"
"Oh, eloquence!
You emerged within me"
"like a wave of beauty."
What did you two want
to say to me?
W-Well..
- This was it.
Y-Yes.
We have nothing else to say.
This was it.
Then I am leaving.
Okay.
See you.
I.. - I am the one who invited
Mira. Why did you come?
You came here asking me
to drop Ammalu.
I didn't do that.
- Did I bring Ammalu here?
Did I? - What?
- Did I?
If you had a little bit
of literary sense
you would have understood
our relationship. - Bullshit!
I am Krishnan.
Mira always worships Krishna.
Not just a worshipper.
She loves him.
You are right.
But the Krishna is only
a minor human incarnation
of the Lord Vishnu.
Mira really worships Lord Vishnu.
Lord Vishnu is Hari.
Hari is Lord Vishnu.
You saying that
won't change anything.
Mira has to decide that, too.
- Who will Mira choose? - Krishna.
No. Hari!
- Krishna! - No.
Hari! - We will see! - No. Hari!
- Krishna! - Hari! - Krishna!
Yes. We will see!
- Okay!
Is this some kind of strike?
Screw the strike!
I am leaving.
I am going to leave.
To where?
- To hell!
Are you Hades to do that?
- Don't mess with me!
Okay. I need to go
to the head office. - Wait.
Head office?
- But we are not done here yet.
The case here won't end
that easily.
I realise that now.
What an investigation!
Is there no other murder case
in the world?
Hari and Krishnan came here..
- Go on.
...to sing and dance
while investigating.
"Pretty woman
with beautiful eyes.."
Mind your words!
- "Sankari, Mouli, Nangeli"
"and other women.."
- Come on. Go to your seats.
Look here, everyone.
I am going to say everything.
All of you go to your seats.
Okay.
What are you saying,
Mr. Sundaran?
I am talking craziness.
Crazy.
Consider
that I cursed you a lot.
Hey!
- Shut up!
You are Hari and Krishnan.
I agree that you are great
and powerful.
But if you're scolded
once in a while when required
you won't be powerful
or great anymore.
I think you are mistaken,
Mr. Sundaran.
I am not mistaken.
I understand everything.
Give me my suitcase.
What case is he talking about?
- I don't know.
That case.
It won't be solved at this rate.
My elder daughter and her husband
are coming from Singapore
Four months pregnant.
Who? - Not the husband.
- Okay.
Okay.
Was that a joke?
Laugh, everyone.
Or I will laugh myself.
Even if my daughter
gives birth 16 times
this case won't end.
I know that.
Do you know why?
- Hey!
I will tell you. - Let's talk.
Come on. - I will.
Okay.
- Let me tell them.
We won't let you say that
in there.
Let go!
If you want to marry
Mr. Vishwambharan's daughter
then let's go.
I will come with you
to propose.
But only one of you
can come with me.
You have to decide
who that person is right now.
Tell me.
Me.
- Me.
If you fight over money,
it can be resolved.
But if you fight over a woman,
nothing can solve it.
I want Hari and Krishnan
to be together always.
What did you decide?
Should I stay or leave?
I understand what you said,
as our big brother.
We won't think of anything else
until this case is solved.
That's a promise.
Me too.
Aren't you leaving now?
- What?
Aren't you?
- I am not. - What?
I have got something.
I will show you.
I have some information about
the six people connected to Guptan.
They are the students of
St. Francis College, Athipuzha.
They know everything
about Mohini Varma.
There is no reason
to stay here anymore.
We have to go live in Athipuzha
without anyone finding out.
Let's go tomorrow.
- Yes. - Okay.
I need to see someone. - Who?
- Who? - I can't tell you that.
So tomorrow we are going to..
- Say goodbye to this place.
I am a lawyer who works
in Harikrishnans Associates.
There are a lot of employees
like me.
Because of you,
Hari and Krishnan
have some desires in their hearts.
You would have known that, too.
If this continues,
they will fight each other
and destroy this establishment.
That's why I am sending them
to Athipuzha tomorrow.
They won't come back.
I am here to apologise
for their actions
and to tell you to forget it.
I can't forget that easily.
I need to know
if their love is true.
If it is, I need to know
who loves me more.
I won't change my mind.
Move.
What?
They have a lot of women
after them.
I am such a woman.
I mean that
I am not going to let
them go that easily.
You don't have to.
Don't tell that I came here
and told you this, okay?
Will you?
- Yes.
What?
- No.
Yes.
- What? - No.
What?
- Yes. - No.
Okay.
This office needs
only two people now.
The rest can go to the head office.
You should take care of everything
and come there.
My daughter and her husband
are coming from Singapore.
Let them come.
I haven't leaked anything
about your journey.
In this journey to find
Mohini Varma
I want to come with you.
We can't be sure about the leak.
Since you came here prepared
we can't stop you.
We don't know how long or where
we are going to stay.
That's all right.
Get in.
Okay. At this rate,
we can decide soon enough.
Thomas Mathew, Stephen,
Radhakrishnan
Sudarsanan, Cletus, Basheer.
These are the six people.
But the connection of them
to a Mohini Varma
is not something we know.
After the murder of Mr. Guptan
none of this six people
has come back to the hostel.
As their warden,
what do you say, sir?
I asked their families.
Most of them contact their families
through the phone.
They said they are on tour.
That signifies a little escape
on the pretext of a tour.
Isn't it?
We don't know that.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
- Welcome. - Thank you very much.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Sundaran.
Those six guys are hiding
somewhere around here.
I am going to fax you
their house addresses.
You have to find their hideout
and inform us.
Only then can we go forward.
We are staying
at the guest house here.
We will eat from the hotel.
You had promised
that you would bring
Mohini to me in nine days.
There are only three days left now.
Yes. The festival in Killikal
temple is only three days away.
I have a lot promises to fulfil
on that day.
But we need these six people
who are the last clue.
They reached Poonoor the day before
Guptan arrived.
In Hotel Vrindavan
they stayed in two rooms.
They followed Guptan daily.
They left the same night
on which Guptan was murdered.
Okay.
Where do you want to stay, Mira?
Is it in the YWCA?
In your guest house.
I will stay there with you.
Is that a problem?
It's not a problem. - It's not.
- It's all right. - It's all right.
There are only two rooms there.
We asked them to clean only one.
The other one is all dusty.
I can clean it up.
It's okay.
We can clean it up.
There!
- Keep it there!
This will be fine.
No. This is
more attractive.
Even this is attractive.
This is fine.
Damn it.
Remove it!
Don't spread that sheet above this.
Even you can't do that.
I won't allow it.
I won't allow you to do that.
Then let's do this.
Let's spread them on either
half of the bed. - Okay, done.
Spread it and feel satisfied.
- Okay.
You won't even let
me do this for her.
Yes, but she will marry me.
I'll be the one to marry her.
No way.
I will marry her.
Do try. She will be sleeping
on my blue sheet tonight.
Come with me at night, and you
may see her sleeping on my side.
I don't need your help.
I will come. - Even me.
Come in, please.
We arranged it all very fast.
If you have any discomfort,
just call me.
Just call me.
- Yes. - Okay.
Goodnight.
- Very goodnight.
See you.
When we wished her goodnight
she said 'see you'.
Did you notice that?
Yes, I did.
Did you notice she hasn't locked
the door? - Yes, I did.
Why would she have done that?
After all, she is an intellectual.
She might be trying
to assess our character.
Let's not be indecent!
Let's bathe and go to bed.
- Yes.
Krishnan.
We should keep in mind that Mira
came here just because
she trusts us. Shouldn't we?
I feel sleepless on thinking of it.
Let's forget about her and sleep.
Isn't it?
- Yes, that's a nice idea.
Hari, I may
become indecent tonight.
Me, too. - What?
- What can we do now?
I have an idea.
It's a bit cheap.
There is no other go.
It's a mutual help which we do
to keep ourselves decent.
Let's sleep with our hands tied.
I feel very happy.
What about you?
Even I feel the same.
My God!
Why did you tie your hands?
Oh! - We wish to be closely
bonded even while sleeping.
It is a practice we follow.
It is a method to protect
our dignity.
This method is very effective.
It is followed by many people
for a long time.
Even I have read many books.
But I am hearing about this
for the first time.
Shall I ask you something?
- Okay. - Yes.
From where do we'll have breakfast?
- From the hotel. - From the hotel.
Won't we be staying here
for two days? - Yes. - Yes.
So I can cook food for you.
What do you say? - Great! - Great!
We don't have anything
to cook food with.
Everything has to be purchased.
- We'll get it. - We'll get it.
Don't go together. Both of you
should purchase things separately.
You should be familiar to deal
with such situations.
I want to know who among you
is better in the role
of a family man.
This is a test.
I..
So fast!
We bought everything.
First, a stove to boil water.
An electric stove.
How will you use an electric stove
during a power failure!
That is useless!
A gas stove is better.
Keeping yourself safe
is more important.
Here is the ointment if you singe
yourself. I brought two.
Utensils designed for safety.
- Gloves to use in the kitchen.
What about food items?
Yes. Salt, mustard, fennel,
pepper, chilly and coriander powder
turmeric, tamarind, Sambar powder,
egg, fish and meat Masala powder
ginger, onion, garlic
and green chilly.
Potatoes, drumsticks, melons
yams, cucumbers, purple yams
taros, tomatoes, curry leaves
Tulsi leaves, lemons, bananas,
pulses, snake gourds
eggplants, ladies fingers, lettuce,
bitter gourds, cabbage
carrots, spinach, beetroot,
cauliflower
elephant foot yams.
Rice, semolina, wheat flour,
millet, maize
black, yellow and green lentils
coffee powder, tea dust, sugar
jam, juice, dish wash soap
cup and saucer, plate, spoon
toothbrush, toothpaste
and toothpicks.
Apples, grapes, oranges,
mangoes, sapodillas
coconuts, jackfruit,
broiler and organic chicken
mutton, beef, bread, eggs and milk.
Utility and chef knives
and axes.
Axe..
Grinding stone, mixer, grinder
casserole, measuring spoons..
Measuring cups..
Enough..
Now let's cook.
- We're ready. - We're ready.
Who says that kitchen work
is only for women?
Man and woman should work together.
Cleaning is the most
important chore.
A man should share work
by helping in cleaning.
See! It's not helping.
It is everyone's duty
to work together.
Enough..
I will do the rest.
I don't know much
about your tastes.
I like hot and spicy food.
I like it a bit sour and salty.
Okay.
Take a bath and get ready.
Here.
I prepared everything
on short notice.
If you don't like it, please
say so. - What's not to like?
I liked it on the first look
itself. - Me too.
Have it.
It is great!
I am not flattering you.
Wonderful!
This is the tastiest food
I've ever had!
Is it too spicy?
- Not at all!
Is it too salty?
Have it all.
Lunch will be late.
Water will ruin your appetite.
Yes. - Yes.
Tasty, isn't it?
Would you like your lunch
to be like this?
Yes. That is good.
Same here. I love it.
I thought
that you would tell me
that it was too spicy
or it was too salty.
But you didn't.
When I realised that
both of you loved me
I came here to know
who loves me truly
and who loves me more.
I was attracted to you
at some point.
Yes, it is true.
But, today I realised something.
There is not even a flicker
of love deep down in your hearts.
You are just competing
with each other.
And neither one of you
is willing to lose.
At the end of your competition,
when both of you win
whom should I choose to
spend the rest of my life with?
Tell me that.
I have just one life.
But I can't give it to you
by dividing it into two.
I have failed in trying
to find real love.
So, let's not continue
this drama anymore.
Put an end to this here itself.
What Mira said is right, isn't it?
- Yes, each and everything.
Our adamancy and competition
have scarred her mind.
We had the complete
freedom to fight each other
and then to solve it
by hugging each other.
Now, Mira is also against us.
One thing is clear.
Mira wanted to accept one of us
into her life.
It is to identify that person that
Mira had tested us today.
But Mira failed.
With tears of failure in her eyes
the question which
Mira asked us today
about the person whom she should
choose to share her life with.
For that question,
we should find an answer today.
Yes, one of us should back out.
Otherwise, that poor girl will not
be able to bear this anymore.
If one of us decide to back out
that will be the
answer to Mira's question.
That answer should
be given at the earliest.
Both of us should not lose Mira.
And one of us will have her.
You may decide it, Krishnan.
We are finding it difficult
to find answers between us.
When I find it difficult to get a
solution for important matters
I usually seek your opinion.
I will do that now also.
You may decide, Hari.
My heart realises that
you love Mira way more than I do.
Again, you just have to
formally tell me
that I should quit.
I am happy to quit for you
with all my heart.
Hari, do you think that I
will say something like that?
You still don't know me, do you?
Maybe I will have a lot of pain
while trying to forget Mira.
But I know that you will suffer
1000 times more pain than I will.
By knowing that fact,
should I ask you to back out?
Should I?
- Yes, you have to.
In the core of my heart
I just have one person
right from the beginning
and that is not
Mira or anyone else.
It is you!
My Krishnan!
And you are more
important than my life.
Hari, no.
I will not ask you to back out.
Only for this issue
I disagree with your decision.
Whatever decision we make will be
like forcing Mira to accept it.
That should not happen.
Let Mira take the decision.
Let her decide
whenever she feels like it.
"The idol opened its eyes"
"and the doors opened by itself."
"The dusk dressed up"
"as a beautiful bride."
"Both the sun and the moon
rose up as the grooms."
"The whole earth stood petrified
at that sight."
"Whom does the dusk belong to?"
"The sun or the moon?"
"The idol opened its eyes"
"and the doors opened by itself."
"The dusk dressed up"
"as a beautiful bride."
"Oh, dusk! Why are your eyes"
"filled with tears?"
"Blessing you with thousands"
"of bright sun rays."
"The sun descends, making"
"way for his friend.."
"For his dear friend."
"The idol opened its eyes"
"and the doors opened by itself."
"The dusk dressed up"
"as a beautiful bride."
"Along this path,
you will always have"
"shining stars around you."
"To love your actions,
you will always have"
"the clouds to accompany you."
"Oh, dusk.."
"Accept the lonely sun"
"as your partner"
"and forget this moon forever."
"The idol opened its eyes"
"and the doors opened by itself."
"The dusk dressed up"
"as a beautiful bride."
"Both the sun and the moon
rose up as the grooms."
"The whole earth stood petrified
at that sight."
"Whom does the dusk belong to?"
"The sun or the moon?"
"The idol opened its eyes"
"and the doors opened by itself."
"The dusk dressed up"
"as a beautiful bride."
You guys seem to be
worried about me.
I don't want you guys
to fight over me.
I'm also not a toy that you guys
can play around with.
At some point, both of you started
loving me for no reason.
Then at some stage,
you say
that neither of you don't want me.
Why are you guys like this?
Have I done anything to hurt you
at any point of time?
Tell me.
Hari loves Krishnan
and Krishnan loves Hari.
A third person has no
place in their lives.
I don't want to be
that third person.
Since we have become so close
I would like to be your friend.
Please agree to my request.
If you find it hard to agree,
it's okay.
I'm used to living alone
and can continue that way.
Mira shouldn't be alone in life.
One of us should be there for her.
- Both of us will be there for her.
One of us as her friend
the other as her partner.
You seem to have taken a decision.
Whom are you going to marry?
Nobody.
I will be their friend.
What is the progress? - I found the
whereabouts of the six-member gang.
Here is the detailed report.
The Sahyagiri estate barn
is their hideout.
They are there.
Mira, before you meet Mohini Varma
there are certain things
you should know.
All that glitters beautifully
might not be gold in reality.
The Mohini you wanted to meet
for all these years
was a lie.
Just like the rainbow.
Mohini is the person who kindled
a spectacular
creativity in Guptan.
A phenomenon that seems
true from far away.
Just like your grandmother
predicted
you will never meet Mohini Varma.
But you might stumble
upon its origins.
Anyway, you should accompany us.
We are going to meet
that mysterious woman.
We are not here to see you.
We are here to know about Mohini
Varma, who got Guptan killed.
Where is Mohini?
Where is Mohini Varma?
We don't know.
- Oh, you don't?
Tell us where Mohini is!
Tell me.
Don't make me beat you.
Tell me, where is Mohini?
The Mohini you are looking
for is him. Sudarsanan.
So you are going to
tell us what happened.
No. Don't ask him anything.
His guilt is driving him crazy.
We are here to stop him
from killing himself.
You will feel a lot better
when you talk openly.
Yes. I will tell you everything.
There is no other way.
Nobody killed our beloved
Mr. Guptan.
He committed suicide
because of me.
Mr. Guptan was a visiting professor
of philosophy at St. Francis.
We became close friends quickly.
He saw life as a beautiful poem.
When we became closer
we found out that he was planning
to become a saint.
We felt that such a person
who appreciates beauty
like him should enter
into wedlock.
When we went to his house,
his father requested the same.
We couldn't understand
the woman of his dreams
even though we tried many times.
That's when we asked Sudarsanan,
who used to write poems
to write poems as a lover to know
the feelings of Guptan.
We heard that he studied
in a college at Indore.
I created a lover,
who wrote poems for him
in the backdrop of the
college at Indore.
Then I transferred her to Delhi.
I gave her the name Mohini Varma.
As Mohini Varma,
I wrote him poems in letters.
He just glanced through
the first few letters.
But when Sudarsanan started
writing poems, he began to notice.
He started to admire Mohini.
To awaken the lover in Mr. Guptan.
And to get him married to a girl
in Mohini's place.
That's all we wanted to do.
He not only loved Mohini
but also wanted to make
her his life partner.
We were devastated when
we came to know this.
We wrote a letter inviting him
to Poonoor to know what he felt.
We never expected him to come.
All we wanted to do was to beg
for forgiveness at his feet.
We told him everything.
What happened next was unexpected.
After hearing all this,
he consoled us.
He appreciated us for creating
a magical world
of love for a short span
of time for him.
He blessed me,
touching my forehead.
When he said goodbye to us
he said he didn't wish
to come down
from the imaginary castles
we made for him.
We didn't know that
those were his last words.
That night, he injected himself
with poison
and jumped onto a pickaxe
from the upper story.
It's all because of me!
It was me!
- Come on. Cheer up.
Come on. Cheer up.
Come on.
Mira, these are magical hands
of Malayalam literature.
This is the hand that gave birth
to the poems that you admired.
Aren't these the hands
that created the beauty
that Guptan admired so much?
These are more gifted
than the hands of Mr. Guptan.
Please don't say that.
If these hands have anything
special about them
that is to have had the chance
to touch Mr. Guptan's feet.
Sudarsanan, where is your house?
He doesn't have a home.
- He is an orphan.
He grew up in an orphanage.
You may be an orphan,
but you can't escape
the responsibility of provoking
Guptan to commit suicide.
No! I won't deny it!
I will punish myself
for killing him.
That is for sure.
- A criminal has no right
to determine his own punishment.
According to the whims
of Guptan's father
or as per the court ruling
you are subject to any punishment,
Sudarsanan.
What are you saying?
- Sudarsanan, are you ready?
I'm ready. - Then stay here
until we are back.
Come.
- Keep an eye on them. - Okay.
No! I won't allow this.
Those kids have done nothing wrong.
Guptan did not kill himself.
He never possessed that
poison found in his body.
Are you trying to make it look
like Guptan committed suicide?
Guptan didn't commit suicide.
Yes. We have to make it look like
that to move forward in the case.
After meeting Sudarsanan
and the others at Poonoor
Guptan was poisoned
when he returned to his room.
Who?
It was Dr. Jaikumar
and his brother Premkumar.
The children of Ramappan,
Guptan's father's distant relative.
Brothers who have
a craving for crime.
Guptan's childhood friends.
The ones who were supposed
to inherit Guptan's property
after he becomes a saint.
They made liabilities worth crores
with that line of thinking.
When they got to know that Guptan
was about to marry Mohini Varma
they lost their peace of mind.
There shouldn't be anybody else
to inherit the property.
When Guptan went to Poonoor
to pick up Mohini Varma
they poisoned him
in his hotel room.
That is the truth.
But that is not what the court
wants to hear.
The court wants evidence.
Evidence is what
they have not left behind.
Does that mean
we cannot apprehend them?
No, we cannot.
This could be the first case
where Harikrishnans
are helpless.
The poison and the syringe
used to kill him
was a mysterious compound created
by the brilliant Dr. Jaikumar.
A secret concoction
of various chemicals
that cannot be detected
by any lab.
That concoction
is the only evidence we have
against them.
Until we receive any information
about that concoction
no matter how hard
we fight against them
no court will not be able
to punish them.
We might just have
to watch the court
setting them free.
What do we do now?
Yes, there is one way.
Just one way.
There should be another situation
such as the one
when Guptan was murdered.
The criminals should be forced
to repeat their crime.
They have to prepare
that deadly concoction again.
We have to apprehend them
along with that poison.
So?
We will have to bring Guptan
back to life.
How?
This plan only has a very
small chance of success.
Let us see how that turns out.
We might have to wait for years
to catch the criminals.
Then we might have
to close this case
considering the incident
to be a suicide.
Don't ask us any more questions.
You have to be at the palace
tomorrow morning.
I am going to inform the Lord
about it.
No, I will go.
You both be there in the morning.
Those boys shouldn't know about
whatever we spoke here.
We won't know what
they could do
once they get to know
about Guptan's killers.
Come.
All of you will stay
with us tonight.
Tomorrow, it is the tenth day
of the festival at the palace.
I gave Guptan's dad my word
that I would apprehend
the criminals on that day.
We will all be going to the palace
tomorrow morning.
Are you ready for that?
Yes, we are.
I have been waiting.
You don't have to introduce
yourselves.
He explained everything to me.
Harikrishnans kept their word.
Well, who among you is Sudarsanan?
Whatever happened was fate.
He was destined to die
at the age of 33.
Let me see the boy that made him
make such a move.
This is Sudarsanan.
What was all this for?
Why did you play such games
with my innocent child?
What had he done to you
that you made him force himself
to commit suicide?
Tell me.
Why did you kill the only person
who was supposed to perform
the rituals after my demise?
Just tell me.
The court can punish him
for forcing him
to commit suicide.
- No.
I don't want the court
to punish them.
He deserves a punishment
that comes from the heart
of a father that lost
his only son.
Do you agree?
Yes, I do.
Then I have decided
the punishment.
For making me lose my son
he will have to stay here
and look after me and the house
all his life.
But don't think that you will get
any bit of our property.
I have decided what to do
with the property.
I won't be able to experience
the sight of the Goddess
appearing in front of us
on hearing Guptan's music
ever again.
So, I have decided to donate
all my wealth
to the temple's trust.
Along with witnessing the Goddess
there will be many documents
signed tonight.
We shall then survive,
surviving on the temple offerings
and live here for all our lives.
This is my decision.
Did everybody get that?
Go to the temple and make
all the arrangements. - Okay.
One moment.
Mira.
This is Dr. Jaikumar
and Mr. Premkumar.
They are Guptan's cousins.
She is Mira.
She is Guptan's friend.
Hello.
Mira..
- What happened, Mira?
When they stood in front of me..
Calm down..
Come.
When I got to know
that Harikrishnans have got
the case,
I was so worried.
But I just got to know
that they are just fools.
Wait, don't just consider
the Harikrishnans to be fools.
They might not seem like much,
but they are devious and crafty.
They may strike out of nowhere.
We have to be very careful.
What can they do now?
What should we be afraid of?
I am not asking you to be afraid.
Think about it.
We have two targets
in front of us now.
One is that boy whom
they have given shelter here.
They have given birth
to another Guptan.
We shouldn't fall for that bait.
The second is the event
where the entire property
will be handed over
to the temple trust.
Don't you see a trap in that?
You have to watch out
for such traps.
It should not happen.
There is no need to prepare
a detailed will.
With the new will, the old ones
become obsolete.
We have an important message
from Chennai.
The board meeting
has been scheduled for tomorrow.
Premkumar and I have to travel
to Chennai as soon as possible.
What are you saying?
Nowadays, there is no one
to manage the affairs here.
Who will make the arrangements
for the function?
It was unexpected.
We cannot miss it.
The train leaves at 7 o'clock
tonight.
What is the point in stopping you
if the work is that important?
Go ahead.
What else can I say?
Where are you going
with your luggage?
We received an unexpected mail.
We are heading to Chennai.
This is bad.
The Lord was happy, thinking
everybody would be here at home.
How can we go there
and tell him that we are going?
So, are you leaving too?
Yes.
- Yes.
They have hundreds
of pending cases.
Why get stuck here?
Let them go.
Go..
Did you write this song,
Sudarsanan?
Yes.
Guptan used to like this
a lot.
Guptan had kept it safe
behind this Veena
and had plans to play
that song tonight.
There used to be a function here
until last year
where the Goddess would appear
and bless them all.
That function cannot
be cancelled this year.
You will sing this song
that you had written
at this palace tonight
with a prayerful mind.
The divine Goddess should appear
in front of us here.
You must possess the belief
and trust for that to happen.
You have it.
All of you must be there
to help Sudarsanan.
We ended up liking Guptan,
though not as much as you.
His poor father is like
a father figure to us now.
If you've done wrong
to that father and his son
this is your chance to correct it.
Don't waste it.
No. Sudarsanan will sing.
I've got this.
Come.
The train will arrive
in 30 minutes.
Make no mistakes.
One of you is Dr. Jaikumar,
and the other is Premkumar
travelling to Chennai
with these tickets.
Raise no suspicions.
Be careful.
Hurry up!
"An evening so rare"
"filled with heavenly music."
"The tunes so mystical"
"are filling our hearts."
"Within my heart"
"are your divine words."
"Oh, Goddess! This life
has fulfilled its purpose."
"An evening so rare"
"filled with heavenly music."
"The tunes so mystical"
"are filling our hearts."
"Your face,
so elegant and graceful"
"resembles the mystical chants
at dawn."
"Your divinity is as vast
as the seven seas."
"Your face,
so elegant and graceful"
"resembles the mystical chants
at dawn."
"Your divinity is as vast
as the seven seas."
"Oh, ever-beautiful one!"
"Thy charms are boundless!"
"Synched into life
are your footsteps."
"Music is the meditation."
"The song is the path."
"Music is the meditation.
The song is the path."
"Your presence is its purpose."
"Spreads a silence,
the oldest form of sound."
"An evening so rare"
"filled with heavenly music."
"The tunes so mystical"
"are filling our hearts."
My Lord! My Lord..
The Goddess is ready
at the temple gates!
They will arrive shortly.
Sing! Don't stop! Sing..
Ask him to sing.
Sing.
Sing. - Sing, man.
- Sing!
What is this? Sing!
Sing!
"Now, the tears shall turn
to tender flowers."
"The sorrows will turn
into a state of bliss."
"Now the tears shall turn
to tender flowers."
"The sorrows will turn
into a state of bliss."
"The darkness of sins
shall dissolve in rays of hope."
"All the good deeds
shall be rewarded."
"Even when helpless,
the divinity within you.."
"...will always give you strength."
"Now, the tears shall turn
to tender flowers."
"Music is the meditation.
- Music is the meditation."
"The song is the path.
- The song is the path."
"Music is the meditation.
The song is the path."
"Your presence is its purpose.
- Your presence is its purpose."
"Spreads a silence,
the oldest form of sound."
"An evening so rare"
"filled with heavenly music."
"The tunes so mystical"
"are filling our hearts."
"Within my heart
are your divine words."
"Oh, Goddess! This life
has fulfilled its purpose."
"An evening so rare"
"filled with heavenly music."
"The tunes so mystical"
"are filling our hearts."
Come!
Wait here. Come.
Come on.
Freshen up and come soon.
Ew!
Thanks.
I'll take the evidence now.
Jai! Prem!
You, whom I raised like Guptan..
Please don't..
An apology..
You!
Come.
You have a chance for payback.
Let's go.
They'll be right back. Come.
Oh, no!
Enough.. You guys go back. You're
needed there. Leave.. Come on.
Where were you?
Stay here. Come here.
Tell me!
How do I thank you?
It's we who are grateful to you
because you did exactly
what we told you.
It's all down
to the Goddess' blessings!
It was extremely difficult
for me to control myself
every time I saw
Guptan's murderers.
Where are they?
- They are standing outside.
The cops have arrested them.
Do you want to see them?
No. Ramappan and his sons!
I don't want to see
those sinners anymore!
I'll lose all the serenity
that I feel in this holy moment.
I won't find it tough
to forget it all now
as he is here.
He is the sole heir
to Killikal palace.
I consider you just
like my dear Guptan!
As you had promised me
you identified Guptan's murderers
and brought them to me.
You brought Guptan
back to me as well.
Let me thank..
No, my Lord!
Please don't.
We consider ourselves
blessed and fortunate
to stand before you right now.
We consider your happiness
as the ultimate treasure!
Then again, shall
we request you something?
Please tell me what it is.
The two of us wish to sleep
in the room which
used to be Guptan's.
Will you please let us do it?
- Is that even a question?
I want all of you to stay here not
for a day, but for a whole month.
What do you say?
- We're ready.
Me, too! - Okay!
- But I need to leave.
My daughter and son-in-law are
coming from Singapore in two days.
Four months pregnant.. - Is it
your son-in-law who is pregnant?
Stop kidding!
Don't ruin this occasion
with your silly jokes.
I know the two of you love
to crack jokes! I know that..
We have to leave tomorrow.
We have another case that needs
to be settled immediately.
It's between us.
It's a difference of opinion.
Bless us to find
the ideal solution to it.
My prayers and blessings
will always be with you.
May the Lord bless you!
We shall take your leave then.
- Okay. - See you. - Bye.
I'll see you in the morning
before we leave.
See you.
Where are they?
They went to settle
the unfinished case
they had mentioned yesterday.
They will be here soon.
You said that you wanted to remain
as our friend, didn't you?
We are ready
to meet you halfway.
What does that mean?
- We agree
that one of us will
always be your friend.
You should
choose who that person is.
Right now and right here.
And then?
He'll have the right to decide
who'll be your better half.
I see.
Tell us.
Is it me or Krishnan?
Whom do you choose
as your friend?
Come on. Is it me or Hari?
Who is it going to be?
You've no plans
to let me be, do you? - No.
Okay. In that case, I need some
time to think about it.
Why do you need time?
We just asked
you to choose a friend.
The decision I make now
should be one that I won't
regret ever in my life.
That's fair enough.
How much time do you need?
At least ten days.
Okay.
We'll be on our way then.
See you.
No goodbyes because
we'll certainly meet again!
No goodbyes since it is quite
possible that we'll meet again.
When my daughter and son-in-law
come from Singapore..
- Shut up! - Get in.. - Shut up!
'Hari. Krishnan.'
Help me choose a friend.
A friend.
Who should I choose as my friend?
'Mira chose
the one who should be her friend'
'and he chose her better half.'
"The full moon welcomes you."
"The nightly birds sing
about your footsteps."
"My mind awaits your consent."
"I await your arrival."
"Won't you come,
beautiful eloquence?"
"I stay silent in the dark night
as the moonlight."
"Don't you remember
our first meeting"
"by the stream where
the water lilies grow?"